Register of the Friedrich A. von Hayek papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Original Accession, 1906-1988
  - Correspondence I, 1923-1988
    - Underberg, Emil, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 54: 4)
    - Undurraga, Vasco [See Chile. Embajada (Germany)]
    - Ungphakorn, Puey, 1963 (Box-folder 54: 5)
    - Union des Jeunes Responsables Economiques (J. J. Orif), 1984-1985 (Box-folder 54: 6)
    - Union of Greek Chambers of Commerce and Industry (Lazaros D. Efraimoglou), 1985 (Box-folder 54: 7)
    - Union Paneuropeenne (Bernd Posselt), 1987 (Box-folder 54: 8)
    - Unione Italiana per il Progresso della Cultura (Renato Pavetto), 1967-1968 (Box-folder 54: 9)
    - United Nations Association in Canada (James Nicholas), 1984 (Box-folder 54: 10)
    - United Nations Association of Great Britain and Northern Ireland (Lord Ennals), 1985 (Box-folder 54: 11)
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development (Frederick F. Clairmonte), 1981 (Box-folder 54: 12)
    - United Nations Education, Science and Culture Organization (Raymond Aron, Andre Lwoff, Amadou-Mahtar M'Bow), 1964-1980 (Box-folder 54: 13)
    - United States. Consulate (Salzburg), 1974 (Box-folder 54: 14)
    - United States. Consulate (Stuttgart), 1963-1977 (Box-folder 54: 15)
    - United States. Department of Justice. Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1954 (Box-folder 54: 16)
    - United States. Department of State. Foreign Service Institute, 1981 (Box-folder 54: 17)
    - United States. Embassy (Austria), 1974 (Box-folder 54: 18)
    - United States. Office of Personnel Management, 1981 (Box-folder 54: 19)
    - Universal Knowledge Foundation, 1963 (Box-folder 54: 20)
    - Universidad Francisco Marroquin (Manuel F. Ayau), 1973-1982 (Box-folder 54: 21)
    - Universidad Interamericana de Puerto Rico (Fernando Zalacain), 1982 (Box-folder 54: 22)
    - Universidad Tecnica Federico Santa Maria (Carlos Francisco Caceres, Juan Naylor W.), 1977-1982 (Box-folder 54: 23)
      Includes correspondence with Pedro Ibanez Ojeda (Fundacion Adolfo Ibanez).
    - Universidade de Brasilia (Carlos Henrique Cardim), 1981 (Box-folder 54: 24)
    - Universität Bayreuth (Wilhelm F. Kasch, Peter Oberender), 1978-1981 (Box-folder 54: 25)
    - Universität des Saarlandes (S. Braga, Dr. Kielwein, Dr. Letzelter), 1963-1964 (Box-folder 54: 26)
    - Universität Salzburg (Theo Mayer-Maly, Herbert Miehsler, Wolfgang Waldstein), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 54: 27)
      Includes correspondence re Hayek's guest professorship.
    - Universite de la Sorbonne, 1983 (Box-folder 54: 28)
    - University of Arkansas (Richard B. Baltz, H. P. B. Jenkins, Paul W. W. Milan, Walter S. Morris), 1950-1979 (Box-folder 54: 29)
    - University of California, Berkeley (Frank Levy), 1975 (Box-folder 54: 30)
    - University of California, Los Angeles (William R. Allen, Rebecca Novelli), 1975-1984 (Box-folder 54: 31)
      Includes correspondence with the Library.
    - University of California, Santa Barbara (Lloyd J. Mercer), 1975-1977 (Box-folder 54: 32)
    - University of Cape Town (H. T. Crouch, J. P. Duminy, G. Hamlyn, Geoff Sargeant), 1960-1967 (Box-folder 54: 33)
      Includes correspondence with the Abe Bailey Trust.
    - University of Chicago (James A. Cunningham, Harvey C. Daines, J. Parker Hall, R. W. Harrison, Robert M. Hutchins, Lawrence A. Kimpton, Donald W. Murphy, John Ulric Nef, Ray Smith, Paul Wheatley), 1948-1983 (Box-folder 55: 1)
      Includes correspondence with the Office of Radio and Television and with the Student Government.
    - University of Chicago Alumni Association, re Chiaki Nishiyama, 1984 (Box-folder 55: 2)
    - University of Chicago Bookstore, 1968 (Box-folder 55: 3)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 55: 4)
    - University of Dallas (Donald A. Cowan), 1975 (Box-folder 55: 5)
    - University of Denver (Edward A. Lindell, Wolfgang Yourgrau), 1966 (Box-folder 55: 6)
    - University of Hawaii (K. T. Fann, Robert W. Hiatt, Robert M. Kamins), 1966 (Box-folder 55: 7)
    - University of London, 1950-1982 (Box-folder 55: 8)
    - University of Michigan Alumni Club of West Germany, 1986 (Box-folder 55: 9)
    - University of Pennsylvania (Lawrence R. Klein, Martin Meyerson), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 55: 10)
    - University of Queensland (D. McL. Lamberton), 1976 (Box-folder 55: 11)
    - University of Reading (Gerard Dummett, Brian Quinn), 1976 (Box-folder 55: 12)
    - University of St. Andrews (Douglas Mason), 1973 (Box-folder 55: 13)
    - University of St. Andrews Conservative Association (D. P. Haselhurst), 1970 (Box-folder 55: 14)
    - University of St. Andrews Philosophical Society (Madsen Pirie), 1970 (Box-folder 55: 15)
    - University of St. Andrews Political Economy Club (Stephen R. Eyres), 1969 (Box-folder 55: 16)
    - University of San Francisco (Chan Young Bang, Robert L. Cunningham), 1963-1979 (Box-folder 55: 17)
    - University of Santa Clara (Mario Belotti), 1975 (Box-folder 55: 18)
    - University of Tennessee at Martin (Charles E. Smith, Gary Young), 1983 (Box-folder 55: 19)
    - University of the Witwatersrand Students' Visiting Lecturers Trust Fund, 1961 (Box-folder 55: 20)
    - University of Vermont (L. A. D. Dellin), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 55: 21)
    - University of Virginia (Leland B. Yeager), 1971 (Box-folder 55: 22)
    - University of Wyoming (Gene M. Gressley, Siegfried Karsten), 1971-1985 (Box-folder 55: 23)
    - University of York (Andrew Dunsire, David Edwards, Susan Mendus), 1981-1985 (Box-folder 55: 24)
    - Unternehmerverband der Industrie Ruhr-Niederrhein, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 55: 25)
    - Utah State University, 1978 (Box-folder 55: 26)
    - Van Dal, A. J. M., 1956 (Box-folder 56: 1)
      Includes correspondence with the International Commission of Jurists and Dudley B. Bonsal.
    - Van den Haag, Ernest, 1962 (Box-folder 56: 2)
    - Vanberg, Viktor, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 56: 3)
    - Vanderbilt, Arthur T., 1956 (Box-folder 56: 4)
    - Varghese, M. P., 1970 (Box-folder 56: 5)
    - Vaubel, Roland, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 56: 6)
    - Veit, Otto, 1965 (Box-folder 56: 7)
    - Velasco, Gustavo R., 1965-1981 (Box-folder 56: 8)
    - Verband Deutscher Maschinen- und Anlagenbau (Otto H. Schiele, Martin Wansleben, Hans-Jürgen Zechlin), 1982-1985 (Box-folder 56: 9)
    - Verdross, Alfred, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 56: 10)
    - Verein Deutscher Ingenieure (G. W. Becker), 1981 (Box-folder 56: 11)
    - Vereinigung für Staatspolitische Mitverantwortung, 1986 (Box-folder 56: 12)
    - Vereinigung Österreichischer Bibliothekare, 1966 (Box-folder 56: 13)
    - Vereinigung Österreichischer Industrieller (Franz Curt Fetzer), 1966 (Box-folder 56: 14)
    - Verosta, Stephan, 1959 (Box-folder 56: 15)
    - Vestuti, Guido, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 56: 16)
    - Via aperta, 1962 (Box-folder 56: 17)
    - Video Arts Television Ltd. (Michael Peacock), 1984 (Box-folder 56: 18)
    - Vietoris, Leopold, 1975 (Box-folder 56: 19)
    - Villey, Daniel, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 56: 20)
    - Viner, Jacob, 1947-1967 (Box-folder 56: 21)
    - Visao Group [See Maksoud, Henry]
    - Voegelin, Eric, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 56: 22)
    - Vogel, Gunter, 1969 (Box-folder 56: 23)
    - Vogel, Heinz-Hartmut, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 56: 24)
    - Vohrer, Manfred, 1978 (Box-folder 56: 25)
    - Voigt, Fritz, 1963 (Box-folder 56: 26)
    - Voit, Erni-Madeleine, 1980 (Box-folder 56: 27)
    - Volkel, Heinz, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 56: 28)
    - Volkmann, Dietrich J., 1979-1980 (Box-folder 56: 29)
    - Volkswirtschaftliche Gesellschaft des Kantons Bern (H. R. Meyer), 1964 (Box-folder 56: 30)
    - Volkswirtschaftlicher Jugend-Ring, 1981 (Box-folder 56: 31)
      Includes issues of Währung und Wirtschaft, 1925.
    - Voluntary Euthanasia Society, 1983 (Box-folder 56: 32)
    - Vorarlberger Volkswirtschaftliche Gesellschaft (Wolfgang Blenk), 1964 (Box-folder 56: 33)
    - Vorort (Kurt Wild, Gerhard Winterberger), 1979-1987 (Box-folder 56: 34)
    - Voswinckel, Ulrich, 1978 (Box-folder 56: 35)
    - Vree, Dale, 1975 (Box-folder 56: 36)
    - Vreede, R. A., 1976 (Box-folder 56: 37)
    - Wachsmuth, Wilhelm, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 56: 38)
    - Wächtershäuser, Günter, 1985 (Box-folder 56: 39)
    - Wagesreither, Edith, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 56: 40)
    - Wagner, Gunther, 1964 (Box-folder 56: 41)
    - Wagner, Helmut R., re Alfred Schutz, 1975 (Box-folder 56: 42)
    - Wagner, Richard E., 1978 (Box-folder 56: 43)
    - Wahl, Rainer, 1980 (Box-folder 56: 44)
    - Waldstein, Wolfgang, 1969 (Box-folder 56: 45)
    - Walker, G. de Q., 1985 (Box-folder 56: 46)
    - Wallich, Henry C., 1963-1983 (Box-folder 56: 47)
    - Walter, Norbert, 1985 (Box-folder 56: 48)
    - Walter Eucken Institut (Alfred Bosch, H. Bosch, Christopher Eucken, Edith Eucken-Erdsieck, Reinhold Veit), 1954-1987 (Box-folder 57: 1)
      Includes correspondence with Ivan R. Bierly, Gunther Heinricke, Franz Josef Hegemann, H. O. Lenel, W. Muller-Freienfels, Kenneth S. Templeton, Jr. (Lilly Endowment), and Richard A. Ware (Earhart Foundation).
    - Walters, Alan, 1984 (Box-folder 57: 2)
    - Wang, Shih-chieh, 1965 (Box-folder 57: 3)
    - Wang, Yichu C., 1955-1974 (Box-folder 57: 4)
    - Warburg Institute, 1986 (Box-folder 57: 5)
    - Warnke, Jürgen, 1983 (Box-folder 57: 6)
    - Washburn, S. L., 1952 (Box-folder 57: 7)
    - Wasielewski, Marion, 1962 (Box-folder 57: 8)
    - Wassenaar, A. D., 1978 (Box-folder 57: 9)
    - Wassermann, Benno, 1987 (Box-folder 57: 10)
    - Watanabe, Takesato, 1981 (Box-folder 57: 11)
    - Watkins, John W. N., 1955-1985 (Box-folder 57: 12)
    - Watrin, Christian, 1964-1984 (Box-folder 57: 13)
    - Wattles, G. M., 1963-1965 (Box-folder 57: 14)
    - Weaver, Carolyn L., 1980 (Box-folder 57: 15)
    - Weaver, Warren, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 57: 16)
    - Weber, W., 1969-1975 (Box-folder 57: 17)
    - Wegener, Hermann, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 57: 18)
    - Wehrschutz, Christian, 1984 (Box-folder 57: 19)
    - Wei, Wellington Y. C., 1966 (Box-folder 57: 20)
    - Weilandt, Gerhard, 1969 (Box-folder 57: 21)
    - Weimer, Walter B., 1976-1983 (Box-folder 57: 22)
    - Weinrich, John E., 1964-1978 (Box-folder 57: 23)
    - Weinzierl, Erika, 1987 (Box-folder 57: 24)
    - Weiss, Dieter, 1983 (Box-folder 57: 25)
    - Weizsäcker, Carl Friedrich von, 1983 (Box-folder 57: 26)
    - Wells, Curt, 1973 (Box-folder 57: 27)
    - Wells, Roger Preston, 1984 (Box-folder 57: 28)
    - Weltbund zum Schutze des Lebens, 1977 (Box-folder 57: 29)
    - Welter, Erich, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 57: 30)
    - Wendt, G. G., 1982 (Box-folder 57: 31)
    - Westdeutscher Rundfunk (Armin E. Moller), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 57: 32)
    - Western Goals Foundation (Lawrence P. McDonald), 1981 (Box-folder 57: 33)
    - Western Quarterly (Francis D. Wormuth), 1956 (Box-folder 58: 1)
    - Westphal, Otto, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 58: 2)
    - Whitaker, John K., 1983 (Box-folder 58: 3)
    - White, Lawrence H., 1980-1985 (Box-folder 58: 4)
    - Whittemore School of Business and Economics (Kenneth J. Rothwell), 1968 (Box-folder 58: 5)
    - Whyte, Lancelot Law, 1966 (Box-folder 58: 6)
    - Wicack(?), Franz, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 58: 7)
    - Wick, Warner A., 1964 (Box-folder 58: 8)
    - Wiese, Ludwig von, 1957 (Box-folder 58: 9)
    - Wieser, Evelyn von, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 58: 10)
    - Wiesner, Joachim, 1983 (Box-folder 58: 11)
    - Wihlborg, Clas, 1980 (Box-folder 58: 12)
    - Wilhelm, Morris M., 1965-1970 (Box-folder 58: 13)
    - Wilkins, Thomas Hart, 1975 (Box-folder 58: 14)
    - Willgerodt, Hans, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 58: 15)
    - William Volker Fund (Ivan R. Bierly, Herbert C. Cornuelle, Richard C. Cornuelle, Floyd Arthur Harper, Harold W. Luhnow, Kenneth S. Templeton, Jr.)
      Includes correspondence with Aaron Director, Loren B. Miller (Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research), Henry C. Simons, University of Chicago, William Johnson, and W. Allen Wallis.
      - 1939-1948 (Box-folder 58: 16)
      - 1949-1952 (Box-folder 58: 17)
      - 1953-1955 (Box-folder 58: 18)
      - 1956-1964 (Box-folder 58: 19)
    - Williams, David A., 1975 (Box-folder 59: 1)
    - Williams, John Burr, 1979 (Box-folder 59: 2)
    - Willits, Joseph H., 1950-1954 (Box-folder 59: 3)
    - Wilmes, Eugen, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 59: 4)
    - Wilson, Colin, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 59: 5)
    - Wilson, Francis G., 1956 (Box-folder 59: 6)
    - Wilson, J. S. G., 1975 (Box-folder 59: 7)
    - Wilton Park International, 1984 (Box-folder 59: 8)
    - Wimmer, Maria, 1984 (Box-folder 59: 9)
    - Winckelmann, J. F., 1963 (Box-folder 59: 10)
    - Windhoek Chamber of Commerce (H. Pupkewitz), 1978 (Box-folder 59: 11)
    - Winkler, Gunther, 1967 (Box-folder 59: 12)
    - Winter Conference on Brain Research (John E. Swett), 1969 (Box-folder 59: 13)
    - Wirtschaftsdienst (Otto G. Mayer), 1976 (Box-folder 59: 14)
    - Wirtschaftsjunioren der Industrie- und Handelskammer Darmstadt (Gerold Schmiedbach), 1983 (Box-folder 59: 15)
    - Wirtschaftspolitische Blätter (Meinhard Supper), 1981 (Box-folder 59: 16)
    - Wirtschaftsrat der CDU (Herbert B. Schmidt), 1969 (Box-folder 59: 17)
    - Wirtschaftsverband Industrieller Unternehmen Baden (Magda Scheffelt), 1977-1986 (Box-folder 59: 18)
    - Wissenschaftliche Hochschule für Unternehmensführung Koblenz (Sonke Albers, Karl Darscheid, Udo Glittenberg, Wolfgang Konig, Hanno Ludwig, Hans-Jürgen Wipfelder), 1984-1987 (Box-folder 59: 19)
    - Wittig, Peter, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 59: 20)
    - Wittkau, Klaus, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 59: 21)
      Includes correspondence with F. Spengelin and Wilhelm Wortmann.
    - Wolf, Joseph Georg, 1969 (Box-folder 59: 22)
    - Wolff, Wolf von, 1963 (Box-folder 59: 23)
    - Woll, Artur, 1967-1984 (Box-folder 59: 24)
    - Wood, Charles Oliver, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 59: 25)
    - Wood County Bank, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 59: 26)
    - Woodell, Professor, 1983 (Box-folder 59: 27)
    - World Congress Alternatives and Environment (Alois G. Englander, Konrad Lorenz), 1979-1987 (Box-folder 60: 1)
    - World Federation of Investment Clubs, 1981 (Box-folder 60: 2)
    - World Future Society, 1984 (Box-folder 60: 3)
    - World Research, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 60: 4)
    - World Wildlife Fund, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 60: 5)
    - Wormald, Avison, re Nikolai Dmitrievich Kondratiev, 1983 (Box-folder 60: 6)
    - Wu, Yuan-li, 1968-1984 (Box-folder 60: 7)
    - Wurdack, E., 1979-1981 (Box-folder 60: 8)
    - Wurtenberger, T., 1964 (Box-folder 60: 9)
    - Yagi, Kiichiro, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 60: 10)
    - Yamagiwa, Masamichi, 1965 (Box-folder 60: 11)
    - Yamanaka, Mr., 1976 (Box-folder 60: 12)
    - Yasui, Takuma, 1970 (Box-folder 60: 13)
    - Yasutake, Masataka, 1964 (Box-folder 60: 14)
    - Yeager, Leland B., 1953 (Box-folder 60: 15)
    - Yin, Fu-sheng, 1965 (Box-folder 60: 16)
    - Yomiuri Shimbun, 1964-1975 (Box-folder 60: 17)
    - Yoneyama, Toshiko and Tohinao, 1980 (Box-folder 60: 18)
    - York University (G. H. McKechnie), 1975 (Box-folder 60: 19)
    - Yoshida, Akira, 1979 (Box-folder 60: 20)
    - Young, J. Z., 1953-1965 (Box-folder 60: 21)
    - Young America's Foundation, 1983 (Box-folder 60: 22)
    - Young Americans for Freedom, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 60: 23)
    - Young Presidents' Organization, 1985 (Box-folder 60: 24)
    - Yuille, Duncan, 1976 (Box-folder 60: 25)
    - Zagorow, Dr., 1964 (Box-folder 60: 26)
    - Zedlitz-Trutzschler, Friedrich Carl, 1977 (Box-folder 60: 27)
    - Zeidler, Karl, 1962 (Box-folder 60: 28)
    - Zeisel, Hans, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 60: 29)
    - Zeleny, Milan, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 60: 30)
    - Zimmer-Lehmann, Georg, 1981 (Box-folder 60: 31)
    - Zinke, George W., 1955-1967 (Box-folder 60: 32)
    - Zipf, Heinz, 1984 (Box-folder 60: 33)
    - Zippelius, Karl, 1984 (Box-folder 60: 34)
    - Zlabinger, Albert H., 1977-1985 (Box-folder 60: 35)
    - Zoller, Michael, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 60: 36)
    - Zollner, Nepomuk, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 60: 37)
    - Zolotas, Xenophon, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 60: 38)
      Includes correspondence with Michael Steinbeisser.
    - Zorn, Franz, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 60: 39)
    - Zuckerman, Irving, 1982 (Box-folder 60: 40)
    - Zundritsch, Otto A., 197(?)-1984 (Box-folder 60: 41)
    - Zweig, Konrad, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 60: 42)
  - Speeches and Writings I, 1939-1982
    Essays, letters to the editor, memoranda, notes, proposals, reviews of Hayek's books, speeches, and related correspondence, arranged chronologically by title.
    - Notes and essay fragments on socialism, holograph, undated (Box 92)
    - "Socialist Planning: Comic Fiction?," typescript, undated (Box-folder 61: 1)
    - "Memorandum on a Bibliography on Time Series Available for Trade Cycle Research, 1820-1914,", 1939
      - Typescript (Box-folder 61: 2)
      - Correspondence with Leon Dupriez, Walther Hoffmann, Tracy B. Kittredge, Robert Marjolin, Charles Rist, and Jan Tinbergen (Box-folder 61: 3)
    - "Some Notes on Propaganda in Germany,", 1939
      - Typescript (Box-folder 61: 4)
        Includes different versions, as well as a draft for a propaganda leaflet in German.
      - Correspondence with Vernon(?) Bartlew(?), Anthony Gishford, John W. Lawrence, Lord MacMillan, F. W. Ogilvie, and John Walter(?) (Box-folder 61: 5)
    - "Historians and the Future of Europe,", 1944
      - Typescript (Box-folder 61: 6)
        Includes notes and distribution list.
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 61: 7)
    - "Memorandum on the Proposed Foundation of an International Academy for Political Philosophy Tentatively Called 'The Acton-Tocqueville Society'," typescript, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 8)
    - "The Prospects of Freedom," typescript and cover letter to Albert Hunold, 1946 October 9 (Box-folder 61: 9)
    - Speech, Mont Pelerin Conference, Mont Pelerin, Switzerland, typescript, 1947 April 1 (Box-folder 61: 10)
    - Memorandum regarding the International Liberal Conference, Wadham College, Oxford, typescipt, 1947 April 9-14 (Box-folder 61: 11)
      Includes suggested constitution for the Liberal International.
    - John Stuart Mill and Harriet Taylor: Their Friendship and Subsequent Marriage, correspondence, 1951, 1952-1970 (Box-folder 61: 12)
    - Review of Charles Morgan, Liberties of the Mind, typescript and correspondence with Alfred J. Suenson-Taylor, 1951 May 19 (Box-folder 61: 13)
    - "Unfinished Draft of a Sketch of a Biography of Ludwig Wittgenstein,", 1953
      - Notes (Box-folder 61: 14)
      - Typescript (Box-folder 61: 15)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1963-1987 (Box-folder 61: 16)
        - Aarhus Universitet, Denmark, 1964 (Box-folder 61: 17)
        - McGuinness, Brian F., 1963-1974 (Box-folder 61: 18)
        - Mills Memorial Library, 1974 (Box-folder 61: 19)
        - Russell, Lord Bertrand, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 61: 20)
        - Shwayder, David S., 1967 (Box-folder 61: 21)
        - Stonborough, John J., 1959-1974 (Box-folder 61: 22)
        - Times Literary Supplement, 1974 (Box-folder 61: 23)
    - Preface to Michael St. John Packe, The Life of John Stuart Mill, typescript, 1953 May 1 (Box-folder 61: 24)
    - "Memorandum on Condition and Needs of the University of Vienna,", 1955 September
      - Typescript (Box-folder 61: 25)
        Includes a form cover letter.
      - Correspondence
        - Barnard, Chester I., 1955-1957 (Box-folder 61: 26)
        - Carnegie Endowment (Joseph E. Johnson), 1956 (Box-folder 61: 27)
        - Drimml, Karl, 1957 (Box-folder 61: 28)
        - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing, 1956 (Box-folder 61: 29)
        - Ettinger, Karl Egmont, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 61: 30)
        - Flexner, Abraham, 1956 (Box-folder 61: 31)
        - Ford Foundation (Alvin C. Eurich, Henry Ford, II), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 61: 32)
        - Inter-National University (Karl J. Ewerts), 1956 (Box-folder 61: 33)
        - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Henry Allen Moe), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 61: 34)
        - Kluver, Heinrich, 1956 (Box-folder 61: 35)
        - Radcliffe, Lord, 1956 (Box-folder 61: 36)
        - Regnery, Henry, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 61: 37)
        - Revay, George, 1956 (Box-folder 61: 38)
        - Richardson Foundation (Frank Barnett), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 61: 39)
        - Rockefeller Foundation (David Rockefeller, Dean Rusk), 1955 (Box-folder 61: 40)
        - Smithsonian Institution (Leonard Carmichael), 1957 (Box-folder 61: 41)
        - United States. Department of State (E. P. Allen), 1955 (Box-folder 61: 42)
        - William Volker Fund (Richard C. Cornuelle), 1955 (Box-folder 61: 43)
    - The Road to Serfdom, Review, 1956 (Box-folder 62: 1)
    - "Why an American Committee for Vienna University," typescript and mimeographed copies with Austrian Institute letterhead, 1957 March 1 (Box-folder 62: 2)
      Includes a list entitled "List of Potential Members of a Committee to Aid Universities in Austria," 1956 December 6.
    - Opening address, 10th Anniversary Meeting, Mont Pèlerin Society, St. Moritz, Switzerland, typescript, 1957 September 2 (Box-folder 62: 3)
    - Two proposals relating to the University of Chicago and the Newberry Library, typescript, 1958 May 27, undated (Box-folder 62: 4)
    - Memorandum relating to the problem of strengthening intellectual efforts in Vienna, Austria, typescript, 1959 March 30 (Box-folder 62: 5)
    - Memorandum relating to the Institute for Advanced Studies in Vienna, Austria, typescript (in German), 1959 June 25 (Box-folder 62: 6)
    - The Constitution of Liberty, 1960
      - Distribution lists, reviews, and correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 62: 7)
      - Japanese edition, typescript preface, 1966 (Box-folder 62: 8)
    - "Proposal for the Creation of an Institute of Advanced Human Studies at Vienna, Austria,", 1960 May
      - Notes (Box-folder 62: 9)
      - Typescript (Box-folder 62: 10)
      - Correspondence
        - Kunz, Josef L., 1960 (Box-folder 62: 11)
        - United States Information Agency (George V. Allen), 1959 (Box-folder 62: 12)
    - Letter to the editor, New York Times, typescript and printed copy, 1961 August 8 (Box-folder 62: 13)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), typescript, 1961 August 8 (Box-folder 62: 14)
      Includes correspondence with editor Geoffrey Woolley.
    - Tribute to Ludwig von Mises, 80th Anniversary Dinner in Honor of Dr. Ludwig von Mises, New York University Club, New York, program, typescript, and correspondence with Lawrence Fertig, 1961 October 17 (Box-folder 62: 15)
    - "Austrian School of Economic Thought," contribution, International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, circa 1966
      - Proofs (Box-folder 62: 16)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 62: 17)
    - "On the Way," typescript, circa 1975 (Box-folder 62: 18)
    - Preface to a collection of essays by David Chow, typescript, 1975 February (Box-folder 62: 19)
    - Dialogue between Hayek and Senmei Nishiyama, published in Chunichi Shimbun, printed copy of the 21-part series (in Japanese), 1976 January 1 (Box-folder 62: 20)
    - "Demokratie und Wirtschaft," speech, Ring Christlich Demokratischer Studenten-Unigruppe-München, Munich, Germany, typescript and announcement, 1976 January 21 (Box-folder 62: 21)
      Includes the introduction of Hayek by Peter Koslowski.
    - "Wohin zielt die Demokratie?," speech, Individuelle Freiheit und Kollektive Wohlfahrt, Konrad-Adenauer-Stiftung, Bonn, Germany, 1976 December 9
      - General (Box-folder 62: 22)
      - Typescript (Box-folder 62: 23)
      - Correspondence with Dieter Oberndorfer and Hans-Joachim Veen, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 62: 24)
    - Inside the Hayek Equation: An Interview with Friedrich von Hayek, printed script of the film made by World Research, 1979 (Box-folder 62: 25)
    - Law, Legislation and Liberty, 1973-1979
      - Volume 2, holograph of pages 115-120, 1976 (Box-folder 62: 26)
      - Volume 3, review, 1979 (Box-folder 62: 27)
    - Letter to the editor, Times (London), printed copy, 198? February 22 (Box-folder 62: 28)